야, 무슨 일이냐?
Hey, what's going on?
문에 쪽지가 붙어있었어
'모니카네로 와'
I found a note on my door,
"Come to Monica's.
'샴페인과 초코렛바
사가지고 올 것?'
Bring champagne
and a Three Musketeers bar"?
그래, 그건 내거다
Yeah, I'll take that.
대체 무슨 일인데?
What's up?
- 모니카와 난 약혼했어
- 세상에
-Monica and I are engaged.
-Oh, my God.
축하한다, 모니카는 어딨어?
Congratulations. Where is she?
나 약혼했다! 나 약혼했다!
I'm engaged! I'm engaged!
She's been there for 20 minutes.
You didn't hear?
20분째 저러고 있었어
올라올 때 못들었어?
난 누가 '나 동성연애한다!'
그러는 줄 알았어
I thought it was a kid yelling,
"I'm gay!"
-Can I bring her in?
-Let her stay. It's sweet.
- 그만 들어오라고 할까?
- 그냥 놔둬, 귀엽잖아
나 결혼할 거다!
나 신부가 될 거다!
I'm getting married!
I'm gonna be a bride!
아니, 입 안 닥칠 거야
난 약혼했으니까!
No, I will not shut up,
because I'm engaged!
오, 허풍쟁이! 여기 와서
나한테 직접 말해보시지 그래?
Oh, big talk! Why don't you
come here and say that to me?
내 약혼자가 너 혼내줄 거다
My fiance will kick your ass.
얼른 와보시지, 20호야, 20호
Come on, apartment 20, apartment 20.
You get her in, you bolt the door,
I'll be in the closet.
네가 데리고 들어와, 넌 문 잠그고
난 옷장 안에 숨어있을께
The One with Monica's Thunder
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
그래, 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐
I just want to say that I love
you guys so, so much...
그냥 너희들 너무나
사랑한다는 말을 하고 싶다
and thank you for being here
on my special night.
오늘 나의 특별한 날에
이렇게 함께 해줘서 고맙구
Our special night.
우리의 특별한 날
It just wouldn't be my night...
Our night...
오늘이 나에게... 우리에게
더욱 특별한 이유는
if you weren't here to celebrate
with me... Us. Damn it!
너희가 여기 나랑 있어서 그래
우리랑, 미치겠네!
It's okay,
I want this to be your night too.
괜찮아
너의 날이기도 해야지
To Monica.
모니카를 위하여
Come on, wait, stop it.
아냐, 그러지 마
Okay, to Monica.
그래, 모니카를 위하여
Have you decided on a band for the
wedding, because I'm kind of musical.
결혼식에서 연주할 밴드에 대해선
생각해봤니? 나 음악성이 좀 있거든
She got engaged a few hours ago,
I doubt she's had time to think...
몇 시간 전에 약혼을 했는데
그거 생각할 시간이 있었겠...
Speaking of chiming in,
remember burning my apartment?
끼어드니까 하는 말인데
내 아파트 태웠던 거 기억해?
Yeah, you're on your own.
이젠 내가 못 도와주겠다
We should get dressed up
and go have champagne at the Plaza.
우리 멋지게 차려입고
플라자에 가서 샴페인 마시자
I can't stay too long.
나 너무 오래는 못있어
I gotta get up early for an audition.
I gotta look good.
오디션 때문에 일찍 일어나야 돼
멋지게 보여야지
I'm supposed to be playing
a 19-year-old.
19살짜리 배역을 맡았거든
What?
뭐?
So when you said get up early,
did you mean 1986?
일찍 일어난다는 게
언제야? 1986년?
You guys don't think I look 19?
내가 19살로
안보인다고 생각해?
오, 열아홉살! 우린 또
아흔살이라고 들었지
Oh, 19! We thought you said 90.
Okay, everybody, let's go.
그래, 다들 빨리 가자
Is my candy bar around here?
내 초코렛바 여기 있었던가?
No, you ate it all.
얘, 다 먹었잖아
I was afraid of that.
그럴까봐 걱정했지
You know what shoes would look great
with this ring?
이 반지랑 딱 어울릴 구두가
어떤 건지 알아?
Diamond shoes.
다이아몬드 구두
You're not getting dressed.
옷 안 갈아입어?
Know what I mean?
무슨 뜻인지 알지?
Yeah, but I don't think we have time.
그렇지만, 그럴 시간이 없는데
There's gonna be a wedding.
결혼식이 거행될 거고
You're gonna be the bride.
넌 신부가 될 거야
200 people are gonna be looking at you
in a clean, white dress.
200명의 사람이 깨끗하고 하얀
드레스 입은 너를 바라볼 거야
Let's do it.
하자
Chandler, it happens to lots of guys.
챈들러, 남자들한테
흔히 생기는 일이야
You're tired,
you had a lot of champagne.
넌 피곤해 있고
샴페인도 많이 마셨잖아
Don't worry about it.
걱정하지 마
I'm not worried. I'm fascinated.
걱정하는 게 아니라
난 신기해 하고 있어
You know? It's like biology.
알겠어? 꼭 생물시간 같잖아?
Which is funny, because in high school
I failed biology...
웃긴 건, 고등학교 때
난 생물을 포기했지
and tonight biology failed me.
근데 오늘 저녁엔
생물이 날 포기했어
Check it out. I could play this
while the guests are coming in, okay.
이거 봐, 하객들이 들어올 때
이걸 연주하면 어떨까? 자...
First time I met Chandler
I thought he was gay
처음 챈들러를 만났을 때
난 그가 호모인줄 알았지
But here I am singing
On his wedding day
근데, 오늘 그의 결혼식 날
난 이렇게 노래하고 있네
Phoebe, no.
피비, 안돼
If you'd let me finish, it goes on
to say that he's probably not gay.
노래 끝나게 해주면, 그가 아마
호모가 아닐 거라는 말이 나와
You guys don't have this problem,
you're made of wood.
너흰 그런 고민 모르겠지
아예 나무로 만들어졌으니까
Hey, you look great.
야, 멋져 보인다
Thanks.
고마워
You okay over there?
너 괜찮아?
I don't know. You know?
I feel a little...
몰라, 있지?
나 조금...
You know what? Never mind.
I'll be fine.
있잖아? 됐어
나 괜찮을 테니까
Don't worry about it. You're probably
tired, you had a lot of champagne.
걱정 마, 넌 피곤해 있을 거야
샴페인도 많이 마셨잖아
It happens to everybody.
모든 사람한테 생기는 일이야
-Happy Monica's Night.
-Well, thank you. You too.
- 해피 모니카 날
- 그래, 고마워, 너도
Can you believe
they are actually getting married?
그 애들 결혼한다는 게
정말로 믿겨지니?
Well, sure,
but I get married all the time.
글쎄 말이야
근데, 난 맨날 결혼하잖아
-You okay?
-Yeah, I guess.
- 너 괜찮니?
- 응, 그래
Do you think we'll ever have that?
우리도 언젠가 그런 날이 올까?
You mean "we," you and me?
'우리'? 너랑 나 말야?
Oh, no, no, no.
오, 아니, 아니, 아니
"We," you with someone,
me with someone.
'우리' 그러니까, 너랑 누구랑
나랑 누구랑 말이지
-Good, you scared me a minute.
-I know. Shake it off.
그래, 잠깐 놀랐다
그래 알아, 그냥 털어버려라
It's just because you and I,
we were like a nightmare.
단지, 우리 사이는
좀 악몽 같았잖아
-No, but there were some good times.
-Absolutely. Like there was...
- 아냐, 우린 좋은 시간도 많았지
- 물론이지, 예를 들어서...
-Surely you can think of something.
-Just give me a minute.
- 설마 한 가지는 생각할 수 있겠지
- 잠깐만 기다려 봐
Oh, well, yes.
오, 그래, 그렇지
I can think of one good thing.
한 가지가 생각났어
You were always good at the...
넌 언제나 말이지...
stuff.
그걸 잘했어
I was good at the stuff?
내가 그걸 잘했다구?
I really liked your hands.
너의 손이 아주 맘에 들었지
My hands?
내 손 말이야?
Way to go, guys.
잘했다, 얘들아
You were really good at the stuff too.
너도 그걸 아주 잘했는 걸
Oh, I know.
어, 나도 알아
Hey, you know what we never did?
야, 우리가
안해본 게 뭔지 알아?
Oh, no, not that.
오, 아니, 그거 말구
We never had a bonus night.
보너스 나이트를 안 가졌어
-A what?
-A bonus night.
- 뭐라고?
- 보너스 나이트
Two people break up, but they
get back together for one night.
두 사람이 헤어지고 나서
딱 하룻밤만 같이 지내는 거 말야
One night, just sex?
No strings attached?
하룻밤을, 섹스만?
아무 조건부 없이?
Yeah, yeah, we never had that.
- 그래, 그래, 그걸 안했어
- 그래
-No.
-Oh.
Okay, this is getting a little crazy.
글쎄, 이거 좀 이상해진다
I'm sure it would be amazing...
물론, 멋질 거라고는 생각하지만
but I really don't think
it would be a good idea.
정말이지, 별로 좋은 생각은
아닐 것 같다
I really...
난 정말로...
really...
정말로...
don't.
그렇게 생각해
Sup?
여어
Sup, dude?
여어, 짜샤
Take whatever you want,
just don't hurt me.
뭐든지 가져가세요
날 해치지만 말아요
You playing
a little PlayStation, huh?
너 지금
비디오 껨 하냐?
That's whack.
그거 쥐기는데
PlayStation is whack.
비디오 껨 쥐기는데
Sup with the whack PlayStation,
sup?
여어, 쥐기는 비디오 껨
여어
Come on, am I 19 or what?
야, 이게 열아홉이 아니면 뭐냐?
Yes, on a scale of one to ten, ten
being the dumbest a person can look...
그래, 1에서 10 등급 중
10이 제일 바보스러워 보이는 거라면
you are definitely 19.
넌 확실히 열아홉이야
Come on, really. How old?
진짜 몇살로 보여?
Young. You're a man-child, okay?
어려 보여
넌 남자 아이야, 됐어?
Now get changed, everybody's ready.
And please, please, keep my underwear.
빨리 갈아입어, 다들 준비됐어
그리고, 제발 내 속옷은 그냥 가져
Thanks.
오, 고맙다
You've had a lot of sex, right?
너 성관계 많이 가져봤지?
When, today?
언제? 오늘 말야?
Some, not a lot.
조금, 많이는 아니고
The reason I'm asking
is because I had kind of a..
내가 묻는 이유는
내가 오늘, 그러니까...
I was unable to..
난 할 수가...
I really wanted to, but I couldn't..
진짜 하고 싶었지만
하지 못했...
There was an incident.
무슨 일이 있었어
Don't worry about that, man.
That happens.
그거 걱정 마, 녀석아
그럴 수도 있는 거야
-It's happened to you?
-Yeah, once.
- 너도 그런 일이 있었어?
- 그럼, 한번
-Well, what'd you do?
-I did it anyway.
- 그래서, 어떻게 했어?
- 그냥 했지 뭐
피비, 어서, 가자
Phoebe, come on, let's go.
얼른
Come on.
왜 아직 옷을 안 입었어?
Why aren't you dressed yet?
네 결혼식을 위한
최고의 노래를 지었어
I wrote the best song
for your wedding.
한 번 들어봐
Check this out.
지금 준비를 하면
결혼식 때 노래하게 해줄께
If you get ready now, you can play.
- 진짜?!
- 그래
-Really?!
-Yes.
너무 신난다! 모니카, 고마워
That's so exciting! Thanks, Mon.
근데, 내 기타에 또 한 번 손대면
널 조금만 때려줘야겠다
But if you touch my guitar again, I'll
have to pound on you a little bit.
알았어, 어서 준비해
다른 사람들 부를께
Fair enough. Get ready.
I'll get everybody.
드디어, 내 축하 파티를 시작...
Finally we can start celebrating my..
미안해, 내가 과거로
이어지는 문을 연 것 같다
I'm sorry, apparently I opened
the door to the past.
있잖아, 모니카
네가 방금 본 것은...
Okay, Monica, Mon.
Okay, what you just saw..
한 가지 묻겠는데
왜 오늘 저녁에 그러는 거지?
Can I ask you just a little question?
Why tonight?
난 이 날을
평생 기다려왔어
I waited my whole life
to be engaged...
어떤 사람과는 달리
난 딱 한 번 약혼할 계획이야
and unlike some,
I only plan on doing this once.
Maybe it's selfish, I'm sorry, but I
hoped tonight could just be about that.
내가 이기적인 건지 모르지만
오늘은 내 약혼에만 집중했으면 했지
But it is just about that.
물론, 네 약혼에만 집중을 하지
Now it's about you
getting back together.
이젠 너희 둘이 다시
커플이 되는 게 초점이잖아
See, you kind of stole my thunder.
내 파티를 가로챈 셈이지
We did not steal your thunder.
We are not getting back together.
네 파티를 가로채지 않았어
우린 다시 커플이 되는 게 아냐
Yeah, no, and you know what?
Nobody even saw.
그래, 그리고, 또
아무도 우리를 못봤잖아
That's true.
그건 그래
-We just kissed.
-It was just a kiss.
- 우린 키스했을 뿐이야
- 그냥 키스였어
You guys kissed?!
너희들 키스했어?!
What does this mean?!
그럼, 그게 무슨 뜻이지?!
Are you back together?
Can I sing at your wedding?
다시 커플이 되는 거야?
결혼식 때 내가 노래해도 돼?
Thunder being stolen.
파티 가로채기 진행 중
-Phoebe, it's nothing.
-Let's not make a big deal of this.
- 피비, 아무것도 아냐
- 괜히 큰일인 것처럼 만들지 말자
It was a one-time thing.
It doesn't even matter.
한 번 그런 것 뿐이야
아무 의미도 없어
Oh, my God.
오, 맙소사
I cannot believe you guys
are talking about this.
어떻게 그런 문제를 갖고
논의하고 있냐?
Problems in the bedroom
are between a man and woman.
침실 사정은
남녀사이의 개인적 문제야
All right? Now, Chandler
is doing the best he can.
알았어? 챈들러는
최선을 다하고 있다구
I don't think that's
what they were talking about.
그거에 대해서 얘기하고
있었던 것 같지 않아
What a great night.
Chandler can't do it, they kissed.
멋진 저녁인데
챈들러는 불능이고 쟤들은 키스했고
-What?
-You guys kissed? This is huge.
- 뭐라고?
- 너희 키스했어? 대단한데
No, it's not huge.
아니, 대단하지 않아
People thinking it's huge
has led Monica to believe...
대단하다고 생각하는
사람 때문에 모니카는
we're stealing her thunder,
which we aren't.
우리가 자기 파티를 가로챘다고
생각해, 사실이 아닌데
We're still talking about it.
아직도 그 얘기
하고 있잖아
That, and Chandler's problem.
그거랑 챈들러의 문제랑
Monica, listen, listen.
모니카, 들어봐, 들어봐
Would you feel better if we stopped
talking about Ross and Rachel?
로스랑 레이첼 얘기 그만하면
기분이 더 좋겠어?
-That would be lovely.
-You got it.
- 그러면 아주 좋겠어
- 그러자구
Now, I can pass for 19, right?
자 그럼, 나 19살로
보일 수 있겠지, 그치?
Yes, you can pass for 19.
그래, 보일 수 있어
-Really?
-Yes.
- 진짜로?
- 그래
-Seriously?
- 진심으로?
- 진심이냐구?
Seriously, no. Okay? You can play
your own age, which is 31.
진심은 아냐, 알았어?
네 나이 31살로 보일 순 있어
I'm 30!
난 30살이야!
Joey, you are not. You're 31.
조이, 아니잖아
넌 31살이야
Oh, crap!
오, 젠장!
So, the Plaza. We'll get some mai
tais? Maybe no more for you though.
플라자 가서 칵테일 마실까?
넌 더 마시면 안되겠지만 말야
You know, I think I don't feel like
going to the Plaza.
있잖아, 나 플라자에
별로 가고 싶지 않아
Monica, this is ridiculous.
모니카, 그러지 마
I don't want to talk about it.
I don't. Especially with you.
더 이상 얘기하고 싶지 않아
진짜로, 특히 너랑은
That is whack.
그거 쥐기는데
I'll play it at the wedding.
이거 결혼식 때 연주할래
We'll see if they actually
let you play.
글쎄 진짜로 연주하게
해줄 건지는 두고 봐야지
They tell you anything
you want to hear...
듣고 싶은 말은
그냥 다 해주잖아
Like, "You look 19."
그러니까
'너 19살처럼 보인다'
Then they just take it away,
like, "No, you don't."
그래 놓고는 '아냐, 안그래'
하고 취소하잖아
Monica won't take this away.
모니카가 이건
취소 안 할 거야
-Wouldn't she?
-Would she?
- 안하겠어?
- 하겠어?
Would she?
하겠어?
You ate my candy bar!
내 캔디 먹었지?
Guess who.
누구게?
Hey, I just realized we kind of left
some stuff up in the air.
아까 우리 몇 가지를
미해결로 놔둔 것 같아서
What did Monica mean:
모니카가 뭘 뜻하는 거였지?
"I don't want to talk,"
especially with me?
'얘기하고 싶지 않아,
특히 너랑은'?
Why not especially you and me?
We were both kissing.
왜 우리 둘한테 안그랬어?
같이 키스하고 있었는데
Still thinking about it?
아직도 그 생각하고 있니?
진짜로 무슨 뜻이야?
'특히 너랑'이 무슨 뜻이냐구?
I'm serious. What did she mean
by that? "Especially you."
-Who cares?
-I care.
- 누가 상관해?
- 내가 상관하지
And so do I.
응, 나도
I have to talk to her.
Will you let me get changed?
물어봐야겠어
나 옷 좀 갈아입을께
Am I going to let you watch me?
내가 옷 갈아입는 걸
구경하게 해준다고 했던가?
No.
아니
I can't believe her.
It's just so typical.
믿을 수 없어
레이첼다운 행동이야
I know you're upset, but don't forget
there is going to be a wedding.
맘 상한 건 아는데 잊지 마
결혼식은 올려질 거야
You are going to throw the bouquet,
and then a honeymoon.
넌 꽃다발을 던질 거고
그 다음엔 신혼여행을 갈 거야
-Maybe in Paris.
-Paris?
- 아마 파리에 갈지도 모르지
- 파리?
We will take a moonlit walk
on the Rue de la blah-blah-blah.
우린 달밤에 뤼 들라
블라블라엘룰루를 산책할 거야
Keep talking.
계속 얘기해봐
We will sprinkle rose petals
on the bed and make love...
우린 장미 꽃잎을 침대에
뿌리고서 사랑을 나눌 거지
not just because it's romantic,
but because I can.
그저 낭만적이어서가 아니라
난 할 수 있기 때문이지
I love you.
사랑해
Don't say anything,
you might scare it away.
아무 말 하지마
놀라서 도망뺄 지도 몰라
It's Paris.
Who knows we're here?
여긴 파리잖아
우리 여기 있는 걸 누가 알지?
Hi, Phoebe. What's up?
안녕, 피비, 무슨 일이지?
You said I could sing at your wedding,
so I need a small deposit.
결혼식 때 노래해도 된다고
했으니까 보증금이 필요해
You know, some good-faith money
to hold the date.
있잖아, 날짜를 잡아놓기
위한 신용 보증금
We're not giving you a deposit
for our wedding.
우리 결혼식인데
너한테 보증금을 왜 주니?
Oh, I see.
어, 알았어
They break your heart, don't they?
진짜 맘 아프게 하지, 그치?
You know, I don't really need
their permission.
난 사실
쟤네들 허락받을 필요 없어
You want to sing at their wedding,
sing at their wedding.
그래, 쟤네들 결혼식 때
노래하고 싶으면 그냥 노래해
Yeah, and if you want to look 19,
then you..
그래, 그리고
넌 19살처럼 보이려면...
You got to do something
about your eyes.
눈에 신경을 좀 써야겠다
What's wrong with my eyes?
내 눈이 왜?
They give you away.
There's too much wisdom in there.
눈은 나이를 못 속이거든
지혜가 너무 많이 보여
Put some tea bags on them
for 15 minutes.
15분간 차 봉지를 얹어놔봐
-That'll get rid of my wisdom?
-Maybe 10 minutes for you.
- 그럼 지혜가 없어질까?
- 넌 한 10분이면 되겠다
Give her the deposit, give her
the ring. I don't care.
그냥 보증금을 줘
반지를 주든지, 다 상관없어!
What did you mean
when you said...
그 말 무슨 뜻이었어?
you didn't want to talk to anyone,
especially me?
'특히 나랑' 논의하고
싶지 않다는 말 말이야
What a great apology.
And you accept it. Bye-bye.
사과 진짜 끝내준다
너 받아들였지? 이제 안녕
No, seriously, what was
the "especially me" part about?
아니, 진짜로
'특히 너'가 무슨 소리냐구?
Let's just say it's not the first time
you've stolen my thunder.
네가 내 파티를 가로챈 것이
이번이 처음이 아니라고 해두자
Hey, here's a thought...
이건 어떻게 생각해...
Monica, what are you talking about?
모니카, 무슨 소리야?
My sweet 16. You went to third base
with my cousin Charlie.
내 16세 생일 파티, 넌 내
사촌 찰리랑 3루까지 갔잖아?
Third base.
아, 3루
It was all everybody could talk about.
그 때 모두들
그 얘기밖에 안하잖아
The only reason I did that
was because your party was so boring.
내가 그랬던 이유는
네 파티가 너무 지루했어서야
We had a caricaturist.
만화가까지 데리고 왔는데!
Whenever I get married
Guess who won't be asked to sing
내가 결혼할 때 노래
부탁받지 않을 자가 누구게?
Somebody named Geller
And somebody else named Bing
'겔러'란 성 가진 사람과
'빙'이란 성 가진 사람이지
Monica, your sweet 16
was like a million years ago.
모니카, 너의 16살 생일은
100만년 전의 일이잖아
Yet here you are doing it again.
근데 넌 또 이러고 있잖아?
I don't want
to steal your stupid thunder.
난 네 바보같은 파티
가로채고 싶은 생각 없어
Why else would you have
made out with Ross?
그럼, 대체 왜
로스랑 그러고 있었어?
Got me.
글쎄다
Easy, mimey, the moment has passed.
It ain't gonna happen.
가만있어, 팬터마임 광대씨
순간은 지났으니까 기대하지 마
It'd be nice if I could
have this night.
난 오늘 밤
딱 하루만 내 꺼였으면 했지
I never wanted any part of your night.
진짜로, 네 밤을
빼앗으려 했던 게 아냐
No one was supposed to see us.
아무도 우릴 봤어도
안되는 거였고
Is that why you did it in the secret
hallway, where nobody ever goes?
그래서 아무도 절대 안다니는
비밀 복도에서 그러고 있었니?
Rachel, I've been thinking.
레이첼, 생각해봤는데 말야
I don't think us getting together
tonight is such a good idea.
오늘밤 우리가 같이 지내는 건
별 좋은 생각이 아닐 듯하다
I'm calling it off.
지금 내가 취소해야겠어
Way to save your dignity, my man.
위신 정말 잘 세운다
이 사람아
Mon, why, why would I ever want
to take away from your night?
모니카, 내가 대체 왜
네 밤을 뺏으려 들겠어?
I don't know, maybe you feel
a little resentful.
몰라, 네가 조금
원망감이 생겼는지 모르지
Maybe you thought
you'd get married first.
네가 먼저 결혼할 거라
생각했는지도 모르고
Maybe you can't stand...
넌 이런 사실을 못참는 걸까?
that your formerly fat friend
is getting married first.
옛날에 뚱뚱하던 친구가 너보다
먼저 결혼한다는 사실 말야
Oh, wow, that.. You know what?
That is so unfair.
와, 그건...정말이지
그건 너무 치사하다
Now I want to steal your thunder.
이젠 네 파티를
가로채고 싶은 맘이 생기잖아
Come on, Ross. Let's go have sex!
이리 와, 로스
가서 섹스하자!
I can't believe you're gonna have sex
on my engagement night.
내 약혼날 저녁에 섹스하다니
정말 믿을 수가 없군!
Well, somebody should.
글쎄, 누군가는 해야지
Look, if we're gonna do this..
이봐, 우리가 이거
할 거라면...
We're not.
She's just gonna think we are.
안해, 하는 것처럼
생각하도록 하는 것 뿐이야
I see, so everybody wins.
아, 그래서
모두가 득보는구나
-Who is it?
-It's Monica, open up.
- 누구야?
- 모니카야, 문 열어
Okay, Ross, stop it.
Please, wait a minute.
오, 로스, 그만해
제발, 잠깐만
Yeah, you like that, baby?
그래, 그거
기분 좋았지, 자기야?
May we help you?
뭘 도와드릴까요?
I wanted to say I hope you have sex,
and I hope you get back together.
이말을 하려고, 둘이 섹스하고
다시 커플이 되길 바란다
I warn you, the night
you announce your engagement...
근데, 내가 경고하건대
너희가 약혼을 발표하는 날
I'm going to announce
that I'm pregnant.
난 임신 사실을
선언할 거야
How is that ever going to happen?
그게 대체 어떻게 가능하냐?
Do you want to know why
I was with Ross tonight?
내가 오늘 밤 왜
로스랑 함께 있었는 줄 알아?
-I know why.
-You don't.
- 알고 있어
- 넌 몰라
-Okay, why?
-Because I was sad.
- 그래, 그럼 왜?
- 난 슬펐기 때문이야
What do you mean?
그게 무슨 뜻이야?
Look, I am so...
이봐, 난 너무나
so happy for you guys.
너무나 기뻐
너희가 약혼한 게
But you getting married reminds me
of the fact that I'm not.
근데 너희가 결혼한다는 사실이
내가 안한다는 걸 상기시키잖아
I'm not even close.
난 가망성도 안보이거든
Maybe I just wanted
to make myself feel better.
그냥 내 자신을
위로하고 싶었나봐
I know that that's dumb,
but you were so depressed...
바보 같은 줄은 알지만
너도 너무 우울해 했잖아
when Ross got married,
you slept with Chandler.
로스가 결혼할 때 말야
그래서 챈들러랑 잤잖아
I don't care, she slept with me.
난 상관 없어
나랑 잤으니까
Anyway, sweetie,
I am so sorry I ruined your night.
어쨌든, 얘
네 약혼날 밤을 망쳐서 미안해
I'm sorry I almost made you
sleep with Ross.
로스랑 자게 만들 뻔해서
미안해
I'm gonna take off.
난 이제 갈께
-Congratulations, man.
-Thanks.
- 축하한다, 이 사람아
- 고맙다
And Rachel...
그리고, 레이첼
what can I say?
뭐라고 할까?
You missed your chance.
넌 기회를 놓쳤어
From now on, the only person who's
going to enjoy these bad boys is me.
이제부터 요 놈들을 즐기는
사람은 나밖에 없을 거야
We thought Phoebe would leave
우린 피비가 떠날 줄만 알았지
But she just stayed and stayed
근데, 계속 머무르고 머물렀지
That's right, I'm here all night
And Chandler will never get..
그래 맞아, 난 여기
밤새 있지롱
챈들러는 이제
절대 못하지롱...
Hey, here's a dollar.
야, 여기 1달러 받아
Consider it a deposit.
Please sing at our wedding.
보증금이라 생각해
제발 우리 결혼식 때 노래해줘
-Oh, thank you.
-Okay.
오, 고마워
Now who will perform the ceremony
누가 주례를 볼 것인가
Who will perform the cer..
누가 주례를 볼 것...
I'll pound on him in the morning.
내일 아침에 때려줘야지